So we’ll have the experience now.
Adesso faremo l'esperienza.
It will take about five minutes
Ci vorranno circa cinque minuti
for you because if all the chakras are discussed
per voi perché, se si è già parlato di tutti i chakra,
already the attention is on that.
l'attenzione è già lì.
Is very simple to put your hands towards Me.
E' molto semplice, tendete le mani verso di me.
Sahaja Yogi : Everyone steps out his shoes, will you ?
Sahaja Yogi : Tutti si tolgano le scarpe, prego.
Shri Mataji : It’s better. [to the Sahaja Yogi].
Shri Mataji : E' meglio. [Al Sahaja Yogi].
You’ve done a good job Ah
Hai fatto un buon lavoro. Ah
Just put your hands towards Me.
Tendete le mani verso di me
Just like this.
in questo modo.
[Shri Mataji takes vibrations of the audience]
[Shri Mataji sente le vibrazioni del pubblico]
Left.
Sinistro.
Now, left hand towards Me and right hand towards the Mother Earth.
Adesso la mano sinistra verso di me e la destra verso Madre Terra.
We’ll give you a balance. You need not close your eyes just now, let’s see.
Vi daremo equilibrio. Non avete bisogno di chiudere gli occhi per ora, vediamo.
Put your right hand towards the Mother Earth.
Mettete la mano destra verso Madre Terra.
As I told you yesterday left side is our conditioning,
Come vi ho detto ieri, il lato sinistro sono i nostri condizionamenti,
conditioning, subconscious and collective subconscious,
condizionamenti, subconscio e subconscio collettivo,
very much at work here.
qui è molto attivo.
But also is an emotional side.
Ma è anche il lato emozionale.
Now put your right hand towards Me and left hand towards the sky.
Adesso rivolgete la mano destra verso di me e la sinistra verso il cielo.
Right hand towards Me, right hand towards Me like this.
La mano destra verso di me, la destra verso di me in questo modo.
Sahaja Yogi : Put your left hand towards the back.
Sahaja Yogi : Rivolgete la mano sinistra all'indietro.
Shri Mataji : Are you feeling the cool breeze in the hand?
Shri Mataji : Sentite la mano destra nelle mani?
You are already thoughtless, there’s no thought,
Siete già senza pensieri, non ci sono pensieri,
but just see if you are feeling the cool breeze.
ma verificate se sentite la brezza fresca.
Sahaja Yogi : It’s better [inaudible].
Sahaja Yogi : Va meglio [non udibile].
Shri Mataji : Much better
Shri Mataji : Molto meglio
Are you?
Vero?
Let’s see.
Vediamo.
[Shri Mataji blows in the mike].
[Shri Mataji soffia nel microfono].
All right?
Va bene?
Are you feeling any cool breeze in the hand?
Sentite la brezza fresca nelle mani?
All right, now put your left hand on top of your head,
Bene, ora mettete la mano sinistra sulla sommità della testa,
just here,
proprio qui,
fontanel bone area.
sull'area della fontanella.
Are you feeling?
Sentite?
It’s a very subtle thing.
E' molto sottile.
Pay attention.
Prestate attenzione.
Shri Mataji : [to the Sahaja Yogi]. Working out ; good?
Shri Mataji : [al Sahaja Yogi]. Funziona; bene?
All right. Now, change over.
Bene. Ora alternate.
See the left hand, with the right hand. Just pay attention there, see.
Sentite la mano sinistra, con la mano destra. Prestate attenzione lì, vedete.
Believe that you are the Spirit.
Credete di essere lo Spirito.
So just you have to say in your heart: “I am the Spirit”, in your heart.
Dovete dire nel vostro cuore: “Io sono lo Spirito”, nel vostro cuore.
Say it seven times, it will work out.
Ditelo sette volte, funzionerà.
Releasing.
Si sta liberando.
Is it all right?
Va bene?
Are you feeling the heat coming out?
Senti uscire il calore?
Little heat.
Un po' di calore.
All right, now turn, change, see now.
Bene, ora giri, alterni e verifichi.
Right Swadhishthan.
Swadhishthan destro.
All right?
Va bene?
Sahaja Yogi : Right Swadhishthan
Sahaja Yogi : Swadhishthan destro.
Shri Mataji : Left [UNCLEAR]
Shri Mataji : Sinistro [non chiaro]
[Shri Mataji washes her hands with water].
[Shri Mataji lava le Sue mani con l'acqua].
Now, just see, if it is working cool breeze…
Ora verificate se funziona la brezza fresca…
[Shri Mataji blows in her hands].
[Shri Mataji soffia nelle Sue mani].
Feel it. Just put your hands like this.
Sentite. Mettete le mani così.
It’s good.
Va bene.
You are all thoughtless. If you see, there’s no thought in your mind.
Siete tutti senza pensieri. Se osservare, non ci sono pensieri nella vostra mente.
And complete silence.
E completo silenzio.
Enjoy this.
Gioitene.
This moment is going to transform your life, take it from Me.
Questo momento trasformerà la vostra vita, credetemi.
You may not realize today but you’ll realize it very soon.
Potreste non rendervene conto oggi ma ve ne accorgerete molto presto.
Ah, strong.
Ah, forte.
Have faith in yourself, that’s the main thing.
Abbiate fiducia in voi stessi, è la cosa principale.
It’s beautiful.
Bellissimo.